<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gerson Uriarte</title>
    <link>https://gersonu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gerson Uriarte</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gersonu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gersonu.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gersonu.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Education I&amp;rsquo;m currently an undergraduate student at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln. Club involvement includes Aerospace Club (division: UAV IARC Team ) and eSAB (engineering student advisory board). The goal of the IARC team is to build an autonomous UAV to compete in the International Aerial Robotics Competition. The goal of eSAB is to facilitate a relationship between engineering students, engineering RSOs(recognized student organization), and the college of engineering as a whole(faculty and staff).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gersonu.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gersonu.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Academic Email: Gersongru@ huskers.unl.edu
Personal Email: Gersongru@ gmail.com
If you would like to contact me by phone number, please refer to the top of my resume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://gersonu.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gersonu.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Project List  WetSpace - mBiTe lab, a website built to house multiple simulation platforms. A user can create an account and use simulation platforms created by the mBiTe team. WetSpace also adds functionality that is not available on each respective simulation platform. Demo WetSpace   Amazon Mturk study - NIMBUS, a website used to run an online study. This website is hosted on my CSE account and was used to run an online HRI study, this study is planned to be done in person soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>